《诉讼双雄》前情提要
依照公司章程第28b条
Pursuant to section 28-b of the bylaws,
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
我提议让哈维·斯佩克特立刻免薪停职
I am placing Harvey specter on immediate unpaid suspension.
但投票的结果可能对你不利
That vote's not gonna go well for you.
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
你的确需要做出谦逊的姿态
You need to do something to humble yourself.
这是什么
What is this?
我希望你替我给
Portfolio of business I want you to take
皮尔逊-斯佩克特的案子
to Pearson Specter for me.
我不会那么做的
I'm not doing it.
是我记错了  还是我们没讨论过这事
Am I mistaken, or did we not have this discussion?
别再打给我了
Don't call me again.
丹尼尔·哈德曼办公室
Daniel Hardman's office.
立刻让他听电话
I need to speak to him right now.
他寄了两个包裹  要么你按照一个继续
He sent two packages. Either move forward
要么他按照另一个继续
on one of them or he'll move forward on the other.
瑞秋  我需要你独自解决这次会议
Rachel, you have to handle this meeting by yourself.
-什么  -她知道我没上过法学院
- What? - She knows that I didn't go to law school.
你要不告诉我发生了什么
I'm calling the DA's office right now
我就给检察官办公室打电话
if you don't tell me what the hell's going on.
我们订婚了
We're engaged.
所以确实是他
So it is him.
求你了  求你了
Please, I am begging you.
完事了
It's done.
-她信了  -是的
- She bought it? - She did.
你觉得我不该再做律师
You think I should stop being a lawyer?
我是说你要真爱她  就不会跟她结婚
I'm saying if you really love her, you won't marry her.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
就是在凝视你的美丽
Just looking at how beautiful you are.
我已经答应了  你不用这么...
I already said yes, so you don't have to--
你今早怎么了
What got into you this morning?
有时我会想我们是如何共同走到这一步的
Sometimes I just think about how we got to be here together.
我会怀疑自己是不是配得上你
Then I wonder if I deserve you.
然后我就会希望我们能赖在这张床上
And then I wish that we could just stay here in this bed
一辈子
for the rest of my life.
我也是
So do I.
这跟之前我们差点
Does--does this have anything to do
被发现有关吗
with the close call we had?
有关
It does.
我觉得没有表达出足够的感谢
I just don't think I ever thanked you enough for...
谢你一直支持我
having my back.
你现在还不知道我会一直支持你吗
Don't you know by now that I will always have your back?
我知道
I do.
哈维  不论结果如何  我们不能表现出软弱
Harvey, no matter how this goes, we don't show weakness,
不能表现出嫌隙  也不能用路易出气
we don't show division, and we don't take it out on Louis.
那会很难  因为我们之所以得开这个会
Well, that's gonna be tough, because we wouldn't even be here
就是因为那个混蛋
if it wasn't for that conniving son of a bitch.
哈维  路易昨晚来找我
Harvey, Louis came to me last night,
说他会更改他的投票的
said he was gonna flip his vote.
不管你原谅他与否  别得罪他
So forgive him or not, don't antagonize him.
你还有机会从这事里脱身
There's still a chance you could get out of this.
早上好  各位
Good morning, everyone.
哈维  在投票之前  你想说点什么吗
Harvey, before we vote, would you like to say something?
好的
I would.
鉴于这次投票的目的
As far as the official purpose of this vote,
我不会用谎言侮辱各位
I'm not gonna insult any of you by lying to you.
我打了路易  我私下也向他道歉了
I hit Louis, and I apologized to him in private,
但我没有做的是向你们大家道歉
but what I haven't done is apologize to all of you.
我的酬金一直对我很重要
My compensation has always been important to me.
并不是因为钱  而是它代表了
Not for the money, but for what it says
我在这家律所的地位
about my place in the firm.
但这不只是间律所  还是个合作关系
But this isn't a firm. It's a partnership.
而我的合作伙伴对我来说要比钱重要得多
And my partners are more important to me than money.
因此从今天开始  我将我的佣金提成比例
So, starting today, I'm reducing my compensation
降低到中间值
to the median amount,
多出的部分分给所有的合伙人
with the rest going to all my partners to share.
不论你们投票的方向如何我都会这么做
And I'm doing this regardless of how you vote today.
感谢各位的聆听
Thank you for listening.
路易  你想提出反对观点吗
Louis, would you like to present an opposing view?
我们速战速决吧
Let's just get this over with.
好的  我们采用不记名投票的方式
Okay. We'll do this by secret ballot.
最终投票结果
The final vote
八票赞成停职  八票反对
is eight for suspension, eight against,
也就是说动议不会通过
which means the motion will not carry.
因此哈维不会被停职
Therefore, Harvey will not be suspended.
好了  如果没别的事
Now, if no one has anything else,
就散会回去工作吧
I would like to get back to business.
事实上  我想要提议
Actually, I would like to propose
一个新议程
a new piece of business.
丹尼尔·哈德曼刚签下了一个十亿级别的客户
Daniel Hardman just signed a billion-dollar client...
-什么  -他提议与我们分享客户
- What? - And in exchange for sharing that client with us,
作为交换条件他想要回到律所
he'd like to return to the firm on a trial basis.
丹尼尔·哈德曼休想踏进这间律所半步
There is no way Daniel Hardman is setting foot in this office.
你肯定会那么想  因为那意味着
Of course you'd think that, because that would mean
我们其余人会挣更多钱
more money for the rest of us.
你在开玩笑嘛  我刚向大家证明了
Are you kidding me? I just showed everyone here
我不在乎钱
I don't care about money.
你刚向我们证明了为了阻止停职
You just showed us that you'll do anything
你不惜一切代价  包括贿赂合伙人
to get out of a suspension, including bribing the partners.
也许你能骗过我们一半人
Well, you may have fooled half of us,
但还有一半人不买账
but the other half didn't buy it.
够了  丹尼尔·哈德曼无论如何
That's enough. Daniel hardman will not return
都不能回来
to this firm under any circumstance.
你当然支持哈维
And of course you back Harvey.
这与哈维无关  这关乎我的律所
This is not about Harvey. This is about my firm.
很明显大家都知道一切都与哈维有关
It's always about harvey and it's clear to everyone here,
他做什么你都觉得无所谓
whatever he does is fine with you,
无论是打合伙人
from hitting another partner
还是拒绝律所数百万的收入
to turning down millions for this firm.
你这个混蛋两面派
You two-faced piece of shit.
为什么不让合伙人们来决定
Why don't we let the partners decide?
不用合伙人来决定
I don't have to let the partners decide,
因为这是我的决定
because this is my decision,
我的决定是  现在休会
and my decision is, this god damn meeting is adjourned!
翻译： 王大可 潇湘月影 木浅薰
翻译：某羽 杨一勾 某茶 菲力
时间轴：风吹来的那片云    校对：油炸电风扇   潇湘月影
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第五季   第九集
你是怎么滚上来的
How the hell did you get up here?
我和楼下的卡尔很有交情
Carl downstairs and I go back.
你可以带着卡尔一起从哪来回哪去
Well, you can take Carl back where you came from.
因为你到这里来需要预约
Because you need an appointment to be here.
我有些东西要交给哈维
I have something I need to deliver to Harvey.
那我建议你把它交给他的秘书  格蕾琴
Then I suggest you leave it with his secretary, Gretchen.
他的秘书  格蕾琴  这几个字我倒是
"His secretary, gretchen." Now, there's three words
从来没想过会从你嘴里说出来
I never thought I'd hear you say.
哈维把你丢给路易
Ooh. How long has it been
多长时间了
since Harvey dumped you onto Louis's desk?
我多久没有扇过你耳光了
How long has it been since I slapped you in the face?
因为现在我脑子里只有这件事
Because that is all I can think about right now.
承诺就是承诺
Promises, promises.
如果你来是要回你的旧办公室  丹尼尔
If you're here to take back your old office, daniel,
先别把尺子拿出来了
don't break out the measuring tape just yet,
因为你渗透回来的路径刚被堵死了
because your plan to worm your way in just failed.
所以你怎么进来就怎么出去吧
So you can walk your ass out the same way you walked in.
路易  看到你和哈维在经历了这么多事以后
Louis, it's so fascinating seeing you and harvey
还能如此团结真是太令人惊喜了
united like this after all you must have been through.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
她啊
Her.
看来你终于在某些事上赢了他
I see you finally got the better of him on something.
我没有在任何事上赢他
I didn't get the better of him on anything.
我们之间不存在什么嫌隙
There's no daylight between us.
赶紧滚出去
Now get the hell out of here.
动作快点  不然我就叫保安
And do it quick before I have to call security
告诉他们我要把你揍得屁滚尿流了
to tell them I'm beating the shit out of you.
不用了
No need.
既然你们对我要说的事不感兴趣
Since you're not interested in what I have to say,
那我就去找杰西卡
I'll go see Jessica.
还有我们悄悄地说
And just between us chickens,
你们俩之间的嫌隙太大了
there's a chasm of daylight between you two.
皮尔逊-斯佩克特的最新晋合伙人过得如何
Hey, how's Pearson Specter's newest partner?
你是说我  还是丹尼尔·哈德曼
Are you talking about me or daniel hardman?
消息传得真快啊
News travels fast.
涉及到人渣的事确实如此
It does when it's news about a lying sack of shit.
迈克  我希望着眼未来的合伙人
Mike, I would hope that a partner with his eye
能更加的宽容一些
on the future would be more forgiving.
你是说欠你人情的合伙人吧
You mean a partner that owes you.
你来不是为了丹尼尔  是为了我吧
You're not here about Daniel. You're here about me.
你猜对了
You're goddamn right I am.
你提拔我只是为获得哈维的信任
You promoted me just to get harvey to trust you
然后有机会陷害他
so you could set him up.
-我没有  -放屁
- No I didn't. - Bullshit.
不  有天赋的律师
No, bullshit is a gifted lawyer being held down
被他所效忠的合伙人压制才叫放屁
by partners to whom he's pledged his loyalty.
这就回到我刚刚说过的话
Which brings me back to what I just said a minute ago.
你自以为收买了我的忠诚
You think you bought my loyalty.
迈克  站哪边随你选
Mike, you can pick whatever side you want,
但当尘埃落定
But when the dust settles,
哈维和杰西卡就会走人了
and Harvey and Jessica are gone,
而你还有立足之地  因为我尊重你
there'll be a place for you here because I respect you.
我来告诉你件事吧  杰克
Let me tell you something, Jack.
等尘埃落定
When the dust settles,
哀求立足之地的是你
you're gonna be the one begging for a place,
而我则会劝他们踢你出去
and I'm gonna be the one recommending they throw you out.
你真该试试那种站式办公桌
You really should try one of those standing desks.
对你这个年龄的女人的背部有好处
It's better on the back for a woman of your age.
对你这种高度的男人  这已经是站式的了
This is a standing desk for a man of your height.
-很高兴见到你  杰西卡  -别装了
- Nice to see you, Jessica. - No, it isn't.
我上次见到你的时候
And the last time I saw you,
警告过你离我的律所远点
I told you to stay the hell away from my firm.
而好律师在面对利益时
And a good lawyer puts aside their feelings
可以抛开私人感情
when there's money on the table.
省省吧  丹尼尔  你从进门那一刻起
Oh, cut the shit, Daniel. Second you get your foot
就已经开始谋划
in the door, you'll start hatching a plan
-怎么把我赶到大街上去了  -说的没错
- to put me on the street. - You're right.
但你作茧自缚  合伙人们无论如何
But thanks to you, the partners will put you
都会把你赶到大街上去了
on the street anyway.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我要与你共享的客户
The client I was willing to share with you
想进行多项收购
is looking to make numerous acquisitions,
而收购来的公司也会成为你的新客户
and those acquisitions would have been new clients for you too.
可你不同意  所以我们会以你们的客户为目标
Instead, we're going to start targeting your clients
进行收购  每家成功收购的公司
as acquisitions, and everyone we close
都会抛弃你们  转投我的怀抱
leaves you and comes right over to me.
所有的合伙人都会知道这是谁的错
And now all the partners will know why it's happening.
而你的走狗  杰克·索罗夫会告诉合伙人
And your puppet, Jack Soloff, tells the partners,
"如果让你回来  血战就会停止"
"If we let you back, the bleeding stops."
这正是我来的原因
Which is why I'm here.
为了谢谢你
To thank you.
要是你当时答应我
It would be so much less delightful
就太没意思了
if you had just said yes right away.
至少你可以告诉我你的第一个目标
Well the least you could do is tell me your first target.
给你个提示
I'll give you a hint.
是家会直接伤你要害的公司
It's one that's gonna hit you right where it hurts.
真不敢相信几个月后我们就要回来
I can't believe that in a couple of months
参加你的婚礼了
we'll be back here for your wedding.
我懂  棒极了  我也难以相信
I know, it's amazing. I can't believe
居然还有那么多事要办
how much we have left to do.
说到这个
Mmm, speaking of which.
这是什么
What's this?
要登在《时代周刊》上的结婚通告
Your wedding announcement for "The Times."
我知道你很忙  所以我就代劳
I know that you're busy, so I took the liberty
帮你写了
of writing it up.
-结婚通告  -没错
- Wedding announcement? - Yes.
妈妈  我觉得...
Um, mom, I don't think that--
有几个地方我留空了
I left a couple of things blank.
我不知道迈克的念的是哪所大学
I wasn't sure where Mike went for undergrad.
是康奈尔还是哥伦比亚
Was it Cornell or Columbia?
他是不是上过哈佛法学院的期刊
Oh, and was he on the Harvard Law Review?
他们还要一张你们俩的合照
And they're gonna want a picture of the two of you.
去中央公园的船屋拍怎么样
I was thinking maybe the central park boathouse?
我们不做结婚通告
We're not doing an announcement.
-什么  -我和迈克对这个不是很感兴趣
- What? - Mike and I, we're not interested in this.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你读你表妹妮可的通告的时候
When you read your cousin Nicole's announcement,
也没见你有意见啊
you didn't have a problem with it.
因为这事符合妮可的风格
'Cause something like this is right for Nicole.
我不喜欢
It's not right for me.
其实是迈克不喜欢吧
You mean it's not right for Mike?
妈妈  你说什么呢
Oh, come on, mom. What are you talking about?
两年前  你根本不会对这个
Two years ago, you wouldn't have had a problem
有任何意见
with something like this.
现在不是两年前
Well, it's not two years ago,
而且我和他都不想弄
and this is how we both feel.
所以我希望你能尊重我的意愿
So I'm just asking you to respect my wishes
因为待办的事还有一大堆呢
because we have so much more to go over, okay?
要我说就是魅力派美妆
I'm telling you it's Cutie Pie Cosmetics.
琼就要退休了
Joan's ready to retire.
没人会在意琼·沃尔什的公司
No one gives a shit about Joan Walsh's business.
肯定是纳德通讯
It's Nader Communications.
为什么  就因为他们是你的客户吗
Why, because they're you're client?
不  因为他们曾是杰克的客户
No, because they were Jack's client
现在是我的客户
and now they're my client.
所以一切都是因为你了
So this is all about you?
-路易  冷静  -不  这都是因为你
- Louis, calm down. - No, this is all about you.
让哈德曼有机可乘的人就是你
You know what? You're the one who gave Hardman the opening he needed.
-你们听到我的话了吗  -你说什么
- Did you hear what I just said? - Excuse me?
你没听错  要不是你想停我的职
Yeah, you heard me. This wouldn't be happening
这一切都不会发生
if you didn't try to suspend me.
那是因为你打我
After you punched me in the face.
你要真想知道元凶是谁
If you really want to know who's at fault here,
不如去照照镜子
why don't you take a look in the mirror?
够了
That's enough.
现在的情形正是哈德曼希望的
This is exactly what Hardman wants.
他想让我们内讧
He's trying to get us to turn on each other.
战争打的是门外人  不是家里人
Well, the fight is out there, not in here,
我们得想出哈德曼的目标是谁
And we have to figure out who Hardman's target is.
你要去哪儿
Where the hell are you going?
你说的没错  战争打的是门外人
You're right, the fight is out there,
但杰克·索罗夫还在门里呢
But Jack Soloff's in here.
让他去找杰克合适吗
You think it's a good idea to let him go after Jack?
他还能干什么  让杰克更疏远我们吗
What's he gonna do? Make him less on our side?
也对
You're right.
这里还有更重要的事要办
There's more important things to do here anyway.
是啊  首要的就是
Yeah, and number one on the list
如果你觉得哈德曼的目标真的是纳德通讯
is if you think that Hardman's really going after Nader Communications,
那我们得过去警告他们
then we need to get over there and warn them.
不是纳德  是麦肯诺汽车
It's not Nader, it's McKernon Motors.
不可能是麦肯诺  他们太小了
It can't be McKernon. They're too small.
电池那单搞定之后就不小了
Not since we did that battery deal.
我知道你想说什么
And I know what you're gonna say,
"艾弗里·麦肯诺的资产
"Avery McKernon's estate still owns
套在股市里的部分太多了"
too much of the stock,"
但现在不是了
but not anymore.
谁收购了
Who bought it?
收购的是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who bought it.
重点是经手的律师是谁
It matters who the attorney of record is.
-我猜猜  丹尼尔·哈德曼吧  -没错
- Let me guess, Daniel Hardman. - Exactly.
见鬼
Goddamn it.
哈维  你要干什么
Harvey, what are you doing?
我要去见多米尼克·巴伦
I'm going to see Dominic Barone.
-那我跟你一起去  -你别去
- Well, then I'm going with you. - No, you're not.
他们是我最老的客户
They're my oldest client,
这事得我去做
and this is something I have to do.
哈维  这客户你已经交给我和路易了
Harvey, this is a client that you gave to me and Louis.
是啊  而你足够聪明
Yeah, and you were smart enough
想到他们就是目标
to figure out they were the target.
现在我要你用那聪明脑子
Now I need you to use that brain
开始想想我们怎么才能摆平这件事
to start figuring out how we're gonna get out of this.
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
我要去看着多米尼克·巴伦的眼睛
I'm gonna look Dominic Barone in the eye
告诉他出这些事都是因我而起
and tell him I'm the reason this is happening.
杰克  我要和你谈谈
Jack, I need to talk to you.
省省吧  路易
You can save your breath, Louis.
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're here to say.
你是来告诉我别对你宝贵的
You're here to tell me not to go against
哈维和杰西卡下手
your precious Harvey and Jessica.
不  我是来告诉你  你根本不了解
No, I'm here to tell you that you have no idea
和你联手的那个人
who you're in bed with.
谢谢你对我的关心
Well, I appreciate your concern for my well-being,
-但我能处理好  -你处理不好
- But I can handle myself. - No you can't.
这有什么区别呢  路易
What difference does it make, Louis?
-为时已晚了  -还不是很晚
- It's too late. - It's not too late.
你觉得如果我突然抛弃了丹尼尔
You think if I suddenly abandon Daniel,
杰西卡就会张开双臂欢迎我回去吗
Jessica's just gonna welcome me back with open arms?
会啊  你都不知道她有多宽容
Yes, you don't know how forgiving she can be.
我相信她  她原谅我的唯一方式
I trust her. The only thing she's going
就是一刀捅死我
to forgive me with is a knife in the back.
杰克  听我说
Jack, listen to me.
丹尼尔·哈德曼曾经把我当儿子对待
Daniel Hardman treated me like a son.
他提拔我为高级合伙人
He promoted me to senior partner,
利用我接管了律所
used me to take over the firm.
他失势后  就过河拆桥
After he lost power, he turns around
甩给我一个性骚扰的罪名
and slaps me with a sexual harassment claim.
我知道  莫妮卡·伊顿
I know. Monica Eaton.
但你不知道的是这些都是胡扯
But what you don't know is that it was bullshit.
他背叛了我
He betrayed me.
羞辱了我
Humiliated me.
在我终于跟他当面对质后
And after I finally confronted him about it,
他告诉我
he tells me...
我是得到了一直想要的东西
that I got what I always wanted.
杰克  相信我  如果你觉得
So, Jack, believe me, if you think this man
这个人在乎你  他根本不在乎
cares about you, he doesn't.
我知道他是什么样的人  路易
I know what kind of man he is, Louis.
那你为什么还站在他那边
Then why are you siding with him?
我告诉你为什么
I'll tell you why.
他对我承诺了杰西卡永远不会做的事
He promised to do something Jessica never would.
让我的名字上墙
Put my name on the wall.
如果她会呢
What if she would?
你太不现实了
You're not in reality.
杰克  她为我这么做了
Jack, she did it for me.
即使我想转换阵营  也做不到
Even if I wanted to go with you, I couldn't.
你有把柄在他手上  对吧
He's got something on you, doesn't he?
这场谈话结束了
This conversation is over.
哈维  什么鬼
Harvey, what the hell?
我刚收到要约收购通知
I just got notification of a tender offer.
他们要对我的公司下手
They're coming after my company.
我知道  所以我才来了
I know, that's why I'm here.
因为这是场恶意收购
So they sent the big guns to fight
所以他们派大人物来了吗
because it's a hostile takeover?
我来这不是因为这是场恶意收购
I'm not here because it's a hostile takeover.
我来是因为整件事都是我的错
I'm here because this whole thing is my fault.
你的错  什么意思
What do you mean your fault?
你被当作目标物是因为
The reason you're in the crosshairs is because
丹尼尔·哈德曼要报复我
Daniel Hardman has a vendetta against me.
你是说  我们刚刚才做了一单
You're telling me we just closed a deal
保证公司未来前景的生意
that ensures this company's future
你就因为惹怒了前合伙人
and you put it in jeopardy because you pissed off
让我们又陷入了险境吗
your former partner?
是的  我就是这个意思
Yes, that's what I'm telling you.
该死的
God damn it.
你指望我怎么做  多米尼克
Well what do you want me to do, Dominic?
我想要你别再像个混蛋一样对待别人
I want you to stop being an asshole to people.
现在说那个太迟了
It's too late for that.
但这个可能还不迟
But it may not be too late for this.
别请我们做代理律师了
Drop us as your attorneys.
什么
What?
只要你跟我们有关系
As long as you're connected to us,
就会被当做攻击目标
there's gonna be a target on your back.
你跟我们撇清关系  可能就安全了
You let us go, there's a chance it goes away.
哈维
Harvey.
如果一有人恨你  我就要跟你撇清关系
If I was just gonna cut you loose because someone hates you,
那我从一开始就不会雇你
I wouldn't have hired you in the fist place,
因为我们都知道
because we both know
我曾经非常恨你
I used to hate you.
谢谢  多米尼克
Thanks, Dominic.
-我们要怎么办  -回头告诉你
- So what are we gonna do? - I'll let you know.
但我把话放在这
But I'll tell you this:
他们想开战  那就开战吧
they want a war, they got a war.
瑞秋  你有路易上个月的尼尔森案简报吗
Hey, Rach, do you have that Neilson brief for Louis from last month?
没有
No, I don't.
你确定吗  因为他一直告诉我在你这
Are you sure? Because he keeps telling me that you have it.
我也一直跟他说我没有
And I keep telling him I don't
我有比每天无所事事地待在这
and I have more important things to do
回答同一个问题更重要的事要做
than sit around and answer the same question every other day.
我也不需要浪费时间在这
And I have better things to do with my time
忍受你这种口气
than to be spoken to that way.
对不起
I'm sorry.
瑞秋  发生什么事了
Rachel, what's going on?
我刚跟我妈妈吃了午餐
I just had lunch with my mom
讨论婚礼的事  她想在《纽约时报》上
to talk about our wedding, and she wants to put
发表结婚通告
an announcement in "The New York Times."
天呐
Oh, my god.
你告诉她不能这么做了吗
Did you tell her that she can't do that?
是的  我编了个谎话说这太势利了
Yeah. I made up some story about it being snobby,
但是唐娜  这只是麻烦的冰山一角
but Donna, that's just the tip of the iceberg.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
这是她提议的宾客名单
This is her proposed guest list.
足有三百人  其中包括
It is 300 people and it includes
首席检察官和哈佛法学院院长
the attorney general and the dean of Harvard Law.
我要怎么办
What am I gonna do?
你得告诉她你不想要
You're gonna tell her that you don't want
太盛大的婚礼  就这样
a big wedding and that's that.
如果我这么说了  她察觉到不对劲的
And if I do that, she's gonna know that something's not right.
瑞秋  每对母女
Rachel, this is the type of argument
都会就婚礼
that every mother has with every daughter
产生这样的争论
about her wedding.
她永远不会想到迈克是冒牌的
She's never gonna think that Mike's a fraud.
-多米尼克反应如何  -还可以
- How'd Dominic take it? - He took it fine.
很好  因为我有计划了
Good, 'cause I have a plan.
说说看
Let's hear it.
我们去个他们绝对想不到的地方
We go to the last place they'd ever expect
-去提合并案  -哪里
- and we offer to merge. - Where?
弗莱彻引擎公司
Fletcher Engines.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我们去找弗莱彻  他们就会踢多米尼克出局
We go to Fletcher, they're gonna kick Dominic out,
杰克就上位了
Jack gains power.
还不如一开始就让麦肯诺被买断
Might as well have let Mckernon get bought out in the first place.
那么唯一有一丝可能的选择
Then the only other option that's even remotely possible
就是把它私有化
is we take them private.
这办法也许真的可行
That actually might work.
回头想想  你为什么不一开始
Come to think of it, why the hell didn't you
就跟我提出这个计划
just say that to me in the first place?
因为我知道不管我第一个主意是什么
Because I knew you'd shit on whatever my first idea was
你都会否决  然后考虑候补计划
and that you'd be open to the backup.
你是说你编了个幌子来操纵我
You're telling me you set up a straw man idea
让我支持你真正的计划
to manipulate me into liking your real idea?
-没错  -你玩这个花招多久了
- Yep. - How long you been doing that?
从皮博迪对丹索普一案起
Peabody versus Danthorpe.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
好吧  小机灵
All right, smart guy.
我们去哪搞买股份的钱
Now where are we gonna get the money for the equity?
让我来告诉你  西德威尔和扬诺普洛斯
I'll tell you where. Sidwell and Gianopolous.
这又是个幌子吗
Is that another straw man idea?
因为你不可能让他们俩
Because you'll never get the two of them
合作商谈  他们互相讨厌
to go in on a deal together. They hate each other.
我就指望他们俩
Oh, those two hating each other is exactly
互相讨厌呢
what I'm counting on.
-妈妈  -瑞秋
- Hey, mom. - Oh, Rachel!
你来的正是时候
You're just in time.
酒席承办商送来了例菜
The caterer dropped off some samples.
我刚准备尝尝  但我们一起品尝
I was just about to try them, but it'll be much more fun
会有趣得多
if we do this together.
妈妈  在你倒酒之前
Okay, mom, but before you pour that.
我觉得脆面包片不太合适
I don't think that the crostini travels very well.
妈妈  拜托
Mom, please.
我知道你为此考虑了很久
I know that you have given this a lot of thought,
但我必须跟你谈谈婚礼的规模
but I need to talk to you about the size of the wedding.
这太盛大了
It's way too big.
我确实考虑了很久
I have given this a lot of thought,
只有三十个人的婚礼
and 30 people at a wedding
可请不到这样的厨师
isn't going to get a chef like this.
没错  但我才不会依着厨师办婚礼
Right, but I'm not having a wedding based on the chef,
我也不是来讨论菜单的
and I'm not here to talk about the menu.
我来是想谈谈宾客名单
I'm here to talk about the guest list.
瑞秋  我告诉过你在我们婚礼三周前
Rachel, did I ever tell you what your father did
你父亲做了什么吗
three weeks before we got married?
他买了两张去百慕大的机票  说我们要私奔
Bought two tickets to Bermuda and said we're eloping.
他那么做是因为他不想
And he did that because he didn't want
应付我的母亲
to deal with my mother.
但你知道什么阻止了我吗
But you know what stopped me?
我知道我一辈子都会后悔
I knew that I would regret doing that to my mom
对自己的母亲做了那样的事
for the rest of my life.
我告诉过你这与迈克无关
But I told you this isn't about Mike,
也不会有什么私奔
and it isn't about eloping.
只是因为我不想
This is just about me not wanting to get married
在数百个陌生人的面前结婚
in front of hundreds of people that I don't know.
到底怎么回事  瑞秋
What's going on here, Rachel?
我都告诉你了
I'm telling you what's going on.
你就是听不进去
You're just not hearing me.
我不想把婚礼搞得这么隆重
I don't want this big of a wedding.
我听明白了  但我了解我自己的女儿
I'm hearing you, but I know my own daughter,
你有事情瞒着我
and there is something that you're not telling me.
好吧  妈妈
Okay, mom.
没错  我确实有事没告诉你
Yes, there is something that I'm not telling you,
因为这件事真的很难开口
and that's because it's really hard for me to say it.
你总觉得这是因为迈克
You keep thinking that this is about Mike.
其实不是
Well, it's not.
是因为你不肯接受这是我的婚礼
This is about you not accepting that it's
不是你的婚礼这个事实
my wedding and it's not yours.
-瑞秋  -如果你不想办法接受这点
- Rachel. - And if you can't figure out a way to accept that,
那我觉得我俩还是私奔吧
then I think maybe we will have to elope.
杰西卡  能跟你谈谈吗
Jessica, can I talk to you for a second?
能等明天再说吗
Can it wait till tomorrow?
不行
No.
我觉得我们应该提拔
I think we should consider promoting
杰克·索罗夫做冠名合伙人
Jack Soloff to name partner.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
杰西卡  现在兵临城下
Jessica, we are under attack.
而你却让我奖赏我们的敌人
And you're asking me to reward our enemy.
不  我是让你把敌人的左膀右臂
No, I'm asking you to bring our enemy's right hand
拉拢到我们这边
over to our side.
路易  时候不早了  我要回家了
Louis, it's late. I'm going home.
杰西卡  你得听我说  求你了
Jessica, you have to listen to me, please.
哈德曼手上有他的把柄
Hardman's got something on him.
什么把柄
Has what on him?
不知道  但两个月前
I don't know, but until two months ago,
我们对杰克·索罗夫的印象还停留在
the only thing we knew about Jack Soloff
他是除我以外计费工时最多的律师
is that he bills more hours than anyone but me.
你觉得他会某天早上醒来
So, what, you think he just woke up one day
突然就变成了政变的幕后主使吗
and became mastermind of a palace coup?
问题的关键不是他们俩谁说了算
The question isn't who's in charge between those two,
而是杰克是自愿的
it's whether Jack is a volunteer
还是被迫的
or a conscription.
我告诉你  我跟他谈过了
I'm telling you, I talked to him.
他做这一切都是被逼无奈
He's doing all this staring down the barrel of a gun.
那么让杰克当上冠名合伙人
Then putting Jack's name on the door
只能给丹尼尔更大的权力
only gives Daniel more power.
你说什么
What are you saying?
如果哈德曼有他的把柄
If Hardman has something on him,
那我们也要抓到他的把柄
then we need to have it on him too.
所以你与其跑来建议我提拔他
So instead of telling me that we should promote him,
不如去找找他的把柄
why don't you get to work on that?
我以为上次谈话时  我已经说的很明白了
I thought I made it clear last time we talked
你说什么我都不感兴趣
I'm not interested in whatever you're selling.
这份你一定会感兴趣的
Well, you're gonna be interested in this.
你摆在我面前的任何交易
There is no deal you're gonna put in front of my face
都不可能让我想跟你合作的
that's gonna make me want to get in business with you.
这不是为了让你跟我做交易
You're not doing it to get in business with me.
而是为了避免我
You're doing it to keep me
跟托尼·扬诺普洛斯做交易
from getting into business with Tony Gianopolous.
因为此时此刻  哈维正在他那里
'Cause, right now, Harvey is over there
向他提出同样的交易
pitching him the same deal.
你以为我在乎哈维·斯佩克特做了什么交易吗
And you think I give a shit what deals Harvey Specter does?
我认为你在乎乔纳森·西德威尔做了什么交易
I think you give a shit what deals Jonathan Sidwell does.
你是来挑拨我俩
And you're here to pit us against each other
好提高价格
just to jack up the price.
说得没错
Damn right I am.
那么你现在就可以走了
Then you can walk your ass out that door right now.
因为我敢保证
Because I guarantee you
西德威尔也是这么对哈维说的
that's what Sidwell's telling Harvey.
哈维正告诉他  你们两个中的一个
And what Harvey's telling him is that one of you
明天会在财经频道上宣布自己的新交易
is gonna be on CNBC tomorrow announcing their new deal...
而另一个将两手空空
And the other one's going to be left with nothing
一无所有
but his dick in his hand,
如何选择取决于你
so, it's up to you.
但先签协议的那个
But whoever calls first is gonna have it
将会压过另一个人一辈子
over the other one for the rest of their life.
时间紧迫啊  托尼
Clock's ticking, Tony.
我收到短信  他就赢了
I get a text, he beats you to the punch.
我立马走人
I walk out that door.
你的决定是什么
So, what's it gonna be?
你真是个混蛋
You're a son of a bitch.
我喜欢
I like that.
我加入
I'm in.
不不  听着  我不在乎他们什么时候需要
No, no, listen. I don't care when they need it.
我每天有十五分钟早餐时间
I get 15 minutes a day to eat my breakfast
可是今天早上没吃成
and I didn't get it this morning.
我刚刚重新加热了我的麦满分
Okay? I just reheated my Egg McMuffin
我现在要安安静静把它吃完
and I'm going to eat it in peace.
你好  小美人
Hello, beautiful.
终于只剩你跟我了
Finally, it's just you and me.
巴纳比  对吧
Barnaby, right?
其实我叫本杰明  我现在...
Actually, it's Benjamin, and I'm kind of on--
我不在乎你在干什么
Oh, I don't care what you're on.
我需要你手上所有关于杰克·索罗夫的资料
I need everything you have on Jack Soloff.
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what that means.
我需要一份
It means that I need a detailed account
他入职至今经手的所有案件的清单
of all the cases he's worked on since he started here.
这是档案室的工作  所以...
Well, that's really more of a file room issue, so--
班森  我要是想去档案室
Hey, Benson, if I wanted to go to the file room,
我就去档案室了
I'd go to god damn file room,
但我没去  因为我还需要所有的工资记录
but I don't because I also want all billing records,
通话记录  私人邮件
phone records, personal e-mails--
私人邮件也要吗
Whoa, personal e-mails?
没错  就算是进行了前列腺检查
Yes. If he scheduled a prostate exam,
也要告诉我
I want to know about it.
这不是每年体检的一项吗
Isn't that just part of the annual checkup?
你哪根葱  卫生局长吗  让你做你就做
What are you, C. Everett Coop? Just get it done.
下次我再让你做什么
And the next time I ask you to do something,
你照做就行  少问蠢问题
do it without asking any stupid questions,
明白了吗
you got it?
迈克·罗斯总会给我带吃的
You know, Mike Ross always brings me food.
什么
What?
我是说  迈克需要我帮忙的时候
I'm just saying, whenever Michael needs a favor,
总会给我带点东西
He brings me something.
比如一袋热培根
You know, like, a warm bag of bacon
或者炸薯条
or french fries.
这不是帮我的忙  这他妈是你的工作
This isn't a favor. This is your god damn job.
赶紧把我要的东西整理好
So get me what I ask for pronto
否则下次我会给你带一袋热翔
or the next time I'll stop by and bring you a warm bag of shit.
现在我连麦满分都不想吃了
And now I don't even want my Egg McMuffin.
唐娜  你有时间吗
Hey, Donna, do you have a second?
当然
Of course.
瑞秋  怎么了
Rachel, what's wrong?
我昨晚跟我妈妈谈过了
I talked to my mom last night.
看来不太顺利
And I take it it didn't go well.
糟透了  我威胁她说要私奔
No, it went horribly, and I threatened to elope.
瑞秋  没事的
Rachel, it's okay.
我们不是谈过吗
Look, we talked about this.
让她觉得你固执
If she's thinking that You're being difficult,
这样她就不会发觉有别的原因
then she's not thinking something else is going on.
是的  可是她看得出来我有事瞒着她
No, no, but she could tell that I'm hiding something
我只好坐在那里骗她
and I had to sit there and lie to her and...
把错都推到她身上
and tell her that it was her fault.
瑞秋  她不会知道迈克的事
Rachel, she's not going to know about Mike.
你不明白
You don't get it.
我在考虑告诉我妈妈真相
I'm thinking about telling my mom the truth.
瑞秋  这不是好主意
Rachel, that is a bad idea.
你妈妈接受得了
Your mom can get over some spat
你对婚礼规模的抱怨
about the size of your wedding,
可她接受不了这个
but she's not going to get over this.
我只知道  我妈妈无论如何都会爱我
All I know is, my mom loves me no matter what.
我理解  但是瑞秋
I understand that, but Rachel,
如果你这么做了
if you do this,
你会让你母亲背负上
you're going to be burdening your mother
一个一生都要
with a secret that she has to keep
对你父亲隐瞒的秘密
from your father for the rest of her life.
你俩怎么进来的
How did you two get in here?
你让我们看到了  你能去我们那里撒野
You showed us you can get to us.
现在你该知道我们也可以来你这里
Now you know we can get to you.
你们一定是来把麦肯诺汽车公司
Then you must be here to hand me the keys
交给我的
to McKernon Motors.
其实  我们是来通知你
Actually, we're here to inform you
麦肯诺汽车公司要转私有了
that McKernon Motors is going private.
那挺好  但问题在于
That's all well and good, but there's the matter
我还是可以投标  最后决定要股东投票
of my tender offer, which is up to the shareholders
而我手里有五分之一股权
and my 20% is voting to take it.
恭喜
Good for you.
我们十分确定剩下五分之四
We're pretty sure the other 80%
都会选择我们的投标  因为
is gonna want to take our offer, seeing as it is
我们的比你的每股高十美元
ten dollars per share higher than yours.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你们哪来的钱
Where'd you get that kind of money?
从想让你滚蛋回泽西联合银行取的
We got it at the united bank of take your ass back to Jersey.
所以想找麻烦请你尽管来  丹尼尔
So, you can keep coming after us all you want, Daniel,
但是结果都会是这样的
but they're all going to end up just like this.
那我就提价
Then I'm going to raise my offer.
每股十美元  因为如果你俩认为
Ten dollars a share, because if you two think
你们能高过我  那你们就错了
you can beat me, you can't.
-跟你说了的吧  -说了什么
- Told you. - Told him what?
那是你的最高价了
That was your ceiling.
他还以为你能每股涨15美元呢
He thought it was 15 a share more.
我以为你还有更大的本事呢
I thought you had bigger balls.
不管怎样  我们只是想知道
Either way, we just wanted to find out
你的封顶是多少以便高出你的
what it was so we could come over the top
粉碎你的计划
and crush you.
因为我们的真实出价是每股涨二十
Because our real offer is 20 more per share
我们也不在乎你的投资人是谁
and we don't care who your investor is,
他们绝无可能出比这高的价
there's no way they're paying more than that
就为了替你报私仇
just to fund your grudge.
回见了  丹尼尔
See you around, Daniel.
对了  迈克在你的盆栽里小便来着
By the way, Mike pissed in your bonsai.
没错  两次
Yeah, that's right. Two times.
顺便说句  引用《非常嫌疑犯》
By the way, nice usual suspects reference
-干的真漂亮  -你听出来啦
- back there. - Really, you caught that?
我当然听出来了  你以为我傻吗
Yeah, I caught it. What do you think I am?
没有  只是以为你听不懂的
Nothing, I just didn't think you'd get it.
我说的很隐晦呀
It was so subtle.
相信我  一点都不隐晦
Trust me, not so subtle.
要真像你说的那么笨拙  那你当时
Well, if it was so ham-fisted, why didn't you just
干嘛不直接戳穿
chime in back there?
因为我是去跟哈德曼宣战
Because I was there to stick it to hardman,
不是为了用暗语和你胡闹的
not clown around with some quote-fest.
这就是我们的区别了
That's the difference between you and me.
两样我可以同时做到
I can do both at the same time.
是吗  以你的年龄
Really? See, at your age,
之前我一直很惊奇你能不去尿尿
I'm surprised that you can even make it through a meeting
一气儿开那么长的会呢
that long without having to pee.
你看  你怎么就非得直白到前列腺上去
Okay, why do you always have to go straight to the prostate?
多么不雅
It's so distasteful.
是吗  那你告诉哈德曼
Oh, right. And you telling Hardman
我在他盆栽里尿尿就能登大雅之堂了
that I'd peed in his bonsai was just pure class.
我可没说你在他盆栽里尿尿了
I didn't say you peed in his bonsai.
我说的是你在盆栽里解手了  你还五岁吗
I said you pissed in it. What are you, five?
还有  是你自己跟他说
And by the way, you're the one who told him
尿了两次的
you did it twice.
因为你已经起头了
Because you started it.
我只好附和你  这叫做有行动力
I had to lean in. It's called committing.
那不如你行动一下  去买下
Then how about you commit to buying the next round
一轮酒吧
for a change?
我是很乐意  但今天不行
I'd love to, but I can't.
我得去瑞秋的妈妈家和她见面
I got to go meet Rachel at her mom's.
谈谈婚礼的事宜
Talk about some wedding stuff.
我很乐意同去
I'd love to join you,
但我宁愿去做前列腺检查
but I'd rather have a prostate exam.
这就对了
There you go.
看吧  你也学会了
See? You're leaning in.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
抱歉  女士  能不能麻烦你
Excuse me, ma'am, could you make sure
等他嘀咕现在都拍不出《欢迎回来科特》
to cut him off when he starts mumbling about
这种好剧的时候
how they don't make shows like
就别让他继续喝了
Welcome Back Cotter anymore?
你来干什么  丹尼尔
What are you doing here, Daniel?
在考虑把这墙漆成什么颜色
Just wondering what color to paint the walls.
从来就不喜欢红色
I've never been partial to red.
你来评论我办公室的墙色
Instead of commenting on my wall color,
还不如回你自己办公室去
why don't you go back to your office?
舔舔自己的伤口
Lick your wounds.
什么伤口  我都要胜利了
What wounds? I'm about to win.
你对胜利的定义真不同常人
You have a funny definition of win.
因为我们刚刚击败了你的最高报价
Since we just blew your best offer out of the water.
这是我新报价的复印件
Here's a copy of my new offer.
明天就会上日报
It'll be in "The Journal" tomorrow.
这交易绝对叫不到这个价
There's no way the deal holds up under this price.
一旦你的委托人想通
And once your client figures that out,
你的投标也就流产了
your offer falls through.
幸运的是  我的委托人是日本人
Well, then lucky for me, my client's Japanese
美元对日元刚刚大幅贬值
and the dollar just took a dive against the yen.
所以我的投标万无一失
So my deal will hold up and then some.
我才不在乎你的委托人是哪里人
You know, I don't give a shit where your client's from.
我绝不会输给你
I don't lose to you.
你会的
Yes you do.
因为这次交易后  还会有下一个
Because after this deal, there'll be another one
再下一个  和再再下一个
and another one and another one,
因为是你夺走了我的律所  而现在
because you took my firm from me and I'm going to take it
我会把它抢回来
right back from you.
滚出我的办公室  丹尼尔
Get the hell out of my office, Daniel,
在我做出让你后悔的事以前
before I do something you'll regret.
提到墙
Speaking of walls,
四周的墙都向你压过来的感觉如何啊
how does it feel to have them closing in on you?
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
路易  出事了吗
Louis, is something wrong?
看到了吗
See this?
这里面是世界上能找到的
It contains everything on god's green earth
关于杰克·爱德华·索罗夫的所有资料
there is to know about Jack Edward Soloff
从他倒霉的八字胡到
from his pirate beard to his stupid pen
他莱纳斯绒毯一样四处显摆的白痴钢笔
that he carries around like linus's blanket.
-结果  -结果完全找不到他的把柄
- And...? - And there's no dirt on him!
没有一个案子他办的不合法
There's not one case he crossed a line on.
没有债务  什么都没有
There's no debts. Nothing.
路易
Louis.
听到我的话了吗  如果索罗夫有把柄
Did you hear me? Is Soloff did something
而哈德曼也知道  那这事埋得太深了
and Hardman's a part of it, it is buried so deep,
让我们连蛛丝马迹都找不到
we'll never even see the top of it,
跟别说追查到底了
let alone get to the bottom of it.
路易  我得给你说一件我原本
Louis, I'm about to tell you something I never
-不打算告诉你的事  -什么事
- thought I would. - What?
哈维和迈克合力想出办法对付
The night that Harvey and Mike put it together
丹尼尔和科斯特尔那晚
about Daniel and CM,
他们嗑药了
they got stoned first.
什么
What?
他们以为你和丹尼尔胜券在握他们已经
They thought you and daniel had them and they were screwed
没法翻盘了就想  管他呢
and they figured, "What the hell?"
所以他们买了大麻嗑了药
So they bought some marijuana and they got high.
你是建议我们现在去买大麻吗
Are you suggesting we take the pot?
对他们就有用啊
Worked for them.
那对我没用
Well, it's not gonna work for me.
-路易  -唐娜  看着我
- Louis-- - Donna, look at me.
你觉得我是需要拥抱和偏执
Do I look like someone who needs to be hungry
-来做事的人吗  -镇定
- and paranoid? - Relax.
我只是提个建议
It was just a suggestion.
那我告诉你这建议很蠢
Well it was a stupid god damn suggestion,
如果你就这一个办法  那你可以滚了
and if that's all you have, just walk you ass out of here.
路易  你怎么啦  干嘛生我的气呀
Louis, what is going on? Why are you so angry at me?
我不是生你的气
I'm not angry at you.
-我是气我自己  -路易
- I'm angry at myself. - Louis.
投票后  哈维跟我说这是我的错
After the vote, Harvey told me it was my fault
知道问题在哪吗  他是对的
and you want to know what? He's right.
哈维说了那么多话
Harvey says a lot of things.
-你也跟我说了  -说什么了
- You told me too. - What?
这件事就是因我而起  因为我告诉了杰克
This whole thing started because I told Jack
他可以把哈维的佣金提出来投个票
that he could bring up harvey's compensation
而你劝阻我来着
for a vote, and you told me not to.
那也许这事也有我的错
Well, then maybe it's my fault too.
因为这件事最根本的起因是
Because this whole thing really started when you tried
你想弥补哈维因为
to make things right with Harvey for
我来为你工作闹的矛盾
me coming to work for you.
唐娜  你是在说你后悔来为我工作了吗
Donna, are you saying that you regret coming to me?
不  路易  我是说也许
No, louis. I'm saying maybe
这事也有我的责任
I had a hand in this too.
现在我们怎么办
What do we do now?
我们一起继续找办法
We keep looking together.
如果找不到  那就告诉杰西卡事实
And if we can't find anything, then we tell Jessica the truth.
劳拉  你好
Laura, hi, how are you?
瑞秋呢  我以为她肯定
Where's Rachel, I thought for sure
会比我早到的
she'd beat me here.
瑞秋不来了
Uh, Rachel's not coming.
我跟她说我有点不舒服
I told her I wasn't feeling well
因为我想跟你单独谈谈
because I wanted to talk to you alone.
出什么事了吗
Is something wrong?
的确
Yes, there is.
瑞秋今天跟我说
Rachel told me today that
她想缩小婚礼的规模
she wants to scale back the wedding
还说这是你们一致决定的
and that you two are in sync on this.
听起来你好像不相信她
Sounds like you don't believe her.
她竟然都不想在《纽约时报》上
Found it hard enough to believe that she wouldn't
结婚通告  这实在让我难以相信
want to put an announcement in "The Times,"
要知道  我的宝贝女儿  可是一直想要
But that my little girl, who always dreamed
在广场酒店举行婚礼的
of getting married at the Plaza Hotel
现在却只要个小型简单的婚礼就好
now only wants a handful of people there?
抱歉  迈克
I'm sorry, Michael.
我不会相信的
I just don't buy it.
这是你的主意  对吗
This is coming from you, isn't it?
被你说中了
You're right.
是我的主意
It is.
让我来告诉你原因
And I'll tell you why.
我没有家人
I don't have a family.
我也没有那么多可以邀请的宾客
I don't have a lot of people that I can invite,
所以我问她是不是可以
and I asked her if we could please
办一个低调点的婚礼
keep the entire wedding low-key.
她说她愿意为了我而牺牲
And she said that she would do that for me.
这我能够理解
And I understand that.
我也觉得她愿意这样为你
I think it's incredibly sweet of her
也真是贴心
to be willing to do that for you.
但是
But...
如果你能主动自愿地
if you could find it in your heart
给我的宝贝女儿一个
to let my little girl have the wedding
她梦寐以求的婚礼  我告诉你
that she's always wanted, I am telling you,
她这一生都不会忘记
she'll remember it for the rest of her life.
又来
Again?
我真的觉得还不如我直接给你把钥匙
You know, I'd really prefer it if I gave you a key
这样我就不用去想你到底是怎么进来的了
so I wouldn't have to wonder how you keep getting in.
我也真心觉得还不如你有事儿没事儿
And I'd really prefer it if you checked your cell phone
就看下手机  也就不用我
every once in a while so that I wouldn't
一直私闯民宅了
have to keep doing this.
-我有手机吗  -有啊
- I have a cell phone? - You do
如果你看了  你就知道丹尼尔·哈德曼
and if you'd check it, you'd know that Daniel Hardman
比我们的竞价高了20%
topped our bid by 20%.
-不可能  -事实如此
- That's impossible. - No, it isn't.
因为美元兑日元的汇率又跌了
Because the dollar took a dive against the yen
而他的客户原来是日本人
and it turns out his client is Japanese.
该死  我们不能输给
God damn it, we are not losing
那个狗日的
to that son of a bitch.
当然  不然你觉得我是为什么来的
Why the hell did you think I'm here?
我们得回去找扬诺普洛斯  争取更多的钱
We need to go back to Gianopolous and get more money.
杰西卡  他不会掏这么多的
Jessica, he's not going to pay that much.
是个脑子正常的人就不会
No one in his right mind would.
那就去找个脑子不正常的人
Then go to somebody who's not in his right mind,
因为那个满嘴假话的混蛋  不把他的名字写回墙上
because that lying bastard isn't going to stop
是不会善罢甘休的
until his name is back up on the wall.
你等等  美元兑日元的汇率下跌
Wait a second, the dollar took a dive
是两周前的事了
against the yen two weeks ago.
说明这里面还有内幕
Which means there's something else going on here.
我来告诉你内幕是什么
Oh, I'll tell you what's going on.
哈德曼一直在玩我们呢
Hardman's been playing with us this whole time.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
我说我得去见个人问点事情
I'm saying I need to go see a guy about a thing.
你去哪儿了
Where were you?
-我去见你妈妈了  -什么
- I was with your mom. - What?
你没收到短信吗  她要推迟跟我们的见面
Didn't you get the message? She had to postpone.
她没推迟  瑞秋  她给我来了个突然袭击
She didn't postpone, Rachel. She blindsided me.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你怎么不告诉我你在跟她吵架
Why didn't you tell me you were fighting with her?
因为妈妈跟女儿本来就会为了婚礼吵架啊
Because mothers and daughters fight about weddings
没什么大不了的
all the time.
但你吵的不是婚礼的事
But you weren't fighting about the wedding.
而是我的秘密
You were fighting about my secret.
那又有什么关系
And what does that have to do with anything?
可是她不知道
Because she doesn't even know it.
因为我想要保护你
Because I'm trying to protect you.
我懂  但这些事你总要
I understand that, but you have to share
-跟我说说  -为什么
- these things with me. - Why?
因为你不但没保护到我
'Cause instead of protecting me,
还把我坑苦了
you hung me out to dry.
此话怎讲
And how exactly did I do that?
你弄的像是我夺走了
By making it seem like I'm the one
你的梦幻婚礼一样
that's taking away your dream wedding.
本来就是你夺走了我的梦幻婚礼
You are the one taking away my dream wedding.
瑞秋
Rachel.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
实在是  太多事了
It's just, it's a lot,
她还想在《纽约时报》上发结婚通告
and she wanted to make this announcement
然后又有长长的宾客名单
in "The New York Times" and had this huge guest list
还要请哈佛法学院的院长  我只是
and the dean of Harvard Law and I just--
我不想你被抓
I don't want you to get caught.
你是不想我被抓
You don't want me to get caught
还是你不想嫁给我
or you don't want to marry me?
什么
What?
我去见克莱尔了
I went to see Claire.
我知道她知道的
I know she knows.
我想知道的是  那有没有
And I want to know if that made you
让你对我们的事  有所犹豫
have second thoughts about us.
你去见克莱尔了  为什么
You went to see Claire? Why...
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me that?
因为她跟我说  如果我真的爱你
Because she told me that if I really loved you,
我就不该娶你
I wouldn't marry you.
我不敢告诉你
And I was afraid to tell you that
是因为我怕你也是这么想的
because I thought maybe you feel the same way.
好吧  但是
Well, it, um,
看来有所犹豫的人好像是你吧
It sounds like you're the one who's having second thoughts.
我没有
No.
我没有过一丝的犹豫
No, I'm not having second thoughts,
但我真的很恨这种感觉  觉得我是在
but I do hate the idea that I am somehow dragging
拖你下水  还是滩可能会毁了你人生的浑水
you into something that is gonna ruin your life.
你没有拖我下任何东西
You are not dragging me into anything
你也没有毁了我的人生  迈克
and you're not ruining my life, Mike.
我不在乎广场酒店  也不在乎宾客有谁
I don't care about the Plaza or who comes or--
那些我都不在乎
I don't care about any of it.
我唯一在乎的是
The only thing that matters to me is that
我要嫁的人是你
the man that I'm marrying is you.
要是你连这一点都剥夺了的话
And if you take that away from me,
我真的
I don't--
瑞秋  瑞秋  听着  看着我  看着我
Rachel, Rachel, listen, look at me, look at me.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
好吗  我们要结婚了
Okay? We're getting married.
婚礼就小办一场
And it could be as small as possible
只请我们的亲朋好友  好吗
with just our close friends, okay?
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
怎么了  路易
What is it, Louis?
我找不到杰克被哈德曼握在手里的把柄
I couldn't find what Hardman has on Jack.
这不应该是你在电梯边上等着
That doesn't sound like something you needed
要告诉我的事儿
to be waiting by the elevators to tell me.
我一直在想  要是我们告诉他
I've been thinking. What if we tell him
要做冠名合伙人  他就得先公开表示
we'll only make him name partner if he takes a public stand
反对丹尼尔  这样的话  就算他
against Daniel first? That way, even if he tries
以后再反对  也没有用了
to go against it later, it won't work.
那你跟他说过了吗
Did you speak to him about this?
-说了  -然后呢
- I have. - And?
他说他愿意
He said he'll be on board.
杰西卡
And Jessica,
我相信他
I believe him.
那告诉他下班后来见我
Then tell him to come see me at the end of the day.
结果我还是要结婚了
Turns out I'm getting married.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我跟我未来的丈母娘说
I was telling my future mother-in-law
我既没朋友也没家人
about how I didn't have any friends or any family
那时候我意识到
when I realized,
不管我们之间发生了什么
whatever happened between you and me...
你对我来说  不是家人  却胜似家人
You're the closest thing to family that I have.
我们见一面怎么样
So what do you say we get together?
-你想见我  -是的
- You wanted to see me? - I did.
我只是想说
I, uh... I just want to say,
基于路易说的  就是你已经准备好了要
based on what Louis said that you're prepared to do--
路易不知道我准备做什么
Louis has no idea what I'm prepared to do
因为我唯一准备做的事情
because the only thing I'm prepared to do
就是给你个机会向耶稣坦诚
is give you a chance to come to Jesus.
而你现在正面对她本人
And you're looking at her.
向耶稣坦诚什么
Come to Jesus about what?
别玩花样了  杰克
Stop tap dancing, Jack.
丹尼尔·哈德曼掌握了你什么把柄
What the hell does Daniel Hardman have on you?
你可以把那个问题问一百万次
You can ask me that question a million times.
但我绝对不会承认所谓把柄存在
I'm never even going to acknowledge its premise.
你刚承认了
And you just did.
如果事情有那么糟  而丹尼尔知道
And if it's that bad, and Daniel knows it
我却不知道
and I don't,
那我就只有一个选择
then I only have one choice.
下面就是我现在要做的事
So, what I'm prepared to do now is this.
你今晚辞职  我免除你的竞业限制
Resign tonight and I'll waive your non-compete.
-你说什么  -你不会真的以为
- What? - Oh, you didn't actually think
我会让你当冠名合伙人吧
I was going to make you a name partner, did you?
那我的回应是
Here's my counter.
你辞职  我免除你的竞业限制
You resign, and I waive your non-compete.
你想让我走  召集投票去
You want me gone, call for a vote.
你想让我走  也得召集投票
You want me gone, you do the same thing
因为我跟你一样是合伙人
because I'm a partner as much as you
而你是陷入困境的那个
and you're the one on the ropes.
我什么也没陷入
I'm not on shit,
因为我们知道丹尼尔的投资人是怎么回事
because we know what's going on with Daniel's investor
而哈维正在去解决问题
and Harvey's about to put a stop to it right now.
如果你真的知道
If you really knew what was going on
丹尼尔跟他的投资人是怎么回事
between Daniel and his investor,
你就该知道永远不可能
you'd know it's never gonna happen.
那我猜我们只能走着瞧了
Then I guess we'll just have to see what we see.....
哈维·斯佩克特  真是惊喜
Harvey Specter. What a nice surprise.
想来一局吗
Wanna play a little pool?
我们这边一局一万
We go for 10,000 a game in here.
你买丹尼尔·哈德曼为你抛头露面
You're playing a lot more expensive game than that,
那游戏玩得比这大多了
funding daniel hardman to be your frontman.
我很欢迎你来证明
And you're welcome to go ahead and prove that,
但他在我两年后离开这里前
but he's got full power of attorney
有全权代理权
until I get out of here in two years.
我不在乎你还有多少年
Yeah, I don't care how many years you have left.
无论多久那都是你最后的日子了
It's about to feel like the rest of your life,
因为这是你要去的地方
because this is where you're gonna spend it.
胡说八道
Bullshit.
只有监狱管理局能移送
Only the Bureau of Prisons can approve a transfer.
但是  我今天去见了肖恩·卡荷尔
I know, but the thing is, I went to see Sean Cahill today.
他想让你在一场审判中作证
Turns out he wants you to testify in a trial.
所以你可以随意
So, you can call the Bureau of Prisons
去找监狱管理局
all you want.
但等到你的律师把你带出去
By the time your lawyers get you out,
你早就变了一个人了
you're never gonna be the same again.
我明白了
I get it.
你希望我停止资助哈德曼
You want me to stop backing Hardman.
而你要继续度你的假
And you go back to working on your break
别再让我见到你
and I don't have to see your face again.
你真是生活在梦里  朋友
You're living in a dream world, pal,
因为那不可能
'cause that's never gonna happen.
那我的建议是
Well then here's my advice.
等你到了雷克岛监狱  直接喝漂白剂吧
When you get to Rikers, drink bleach.
能帮你进医务室
It'll get you sent to the infirmary.
那里要安全得多
It's much safer there.
我不用进医务室
Oh, I don't need to go to the infirmary
因为我有能保证我
'cause I got something that's gonna keep me
像在妈妈臂弯里一样安全的东西
as safe as a baby in his mother's arms.
钱
Money.
你可以试试运气  查尔斯
You take that chance, Charles,
可只要有一个人
but if there's one guy
不在乎你的臭钱
who doesn't give a shit about your money,
他就会收拾你  而没人会阻止他
he's gonna get you, and nobody's gonna stop him.
但问题是  哈维
Here's the thing, Harvey.
没人不在乎钱
Nobody doesn't give a shit about money.
而且  不到一周  我就会回到这里
Besides, in a week, I'll be right back here
一个接一个抢走你们的客户
picking off your clients one by one.
你想阻止我  就辞职
You want to stop me, step down.
-你说什么  -你辞职
- What? - You resign,
他的钱就没了
His money goes away.
我就知道
I knew it.
你关心那里的人
You care about the people there,
就像你当年关心你的小弟弟一样
just like you cared about your little brother way back when.
不可能
No way.
我不同意
No deal.
在你给我答复之前我要说
Now, before you give me an answer--
你今晚来这里  是因为你知道
you came here tonight because you know
你无论如何都会输
you're gonna lose anyway.
那为什么不在自己还可以的时候
So why not save whatever poor sap it is
救下最后一点点力量呢
while you still can?
我为什么要相信你真的会
Why should I believe you would even live up
实现你的承诺呢
to your end of the bargain?
因为我根本不在乎
Because I don't give a shit about your war
你跟丹尼尔·哈德曼的斗争
with Daniel Hardman.
我也非常确定我更不在乎
And I sure as hell don't give a shit
你的律所
about your firm.
我想要的只是看着你跪下
All I want to do is see you get down
然后说  "我退出"
on your knees and say, "I quit."
特雷弗
Trevor.
迈克
Hey, Mike.
-谢谢你能来  -没什么
- Thanks for coming. - Yeah, hey,
-我很高兴你打给我  -我也是
- I'm glad you called. - Yeah, me too.
说起来  上次见面
Listen, uh, about the last time,
我说了些
I said some things--
我们都说了过分的话
Ah, we both said some things.
而我做得过分了  我很抱歉
But I did some things. And I'm sorry.
我有个机会让你补偿我
Well, uh, I have a way you can make it up to me.
来我的婚礼吧
Come to my wedding.
你希望我出席  对我意义重大
It means a lot to me that you want me there,
但是对不起
but I'm sorry.
我不能去
I can't.
不能去是什么意思
What do you mean you can't?
我已经结婚了
Look, I'm married now,
我跟我妻子承诺说过去那部分生活
and I promised my wife that that part of my life
已经完全过去了
is behind me.
那跟你来我的婚礼有什么关系呢
What does that have to do with you coming to my wedding?
她都不同意我来这儿见你
She didn't even want me to meet you here.
你不明白吗
Don't you get it?
你在违法
You're breaking the law
每天都在
every day.
-你在指责我  -不
- You're judging me? - No.
我不是指责你
I'm not judging you.
没什么能比让我举杯庆祝你的新生活
Nothing would make me happier than to raise a glass
更能让我开心的
to your new life,
但我不能
But I can't.
你也不应该
And you shouldn't either.
所以我不该结婚了
Oh, so now I shouldn't get married?
不  我是说你应该辞职
No, I'm saying you should quit.
好吧
Oh, okay.
谢谢你的建议  特雷弗
Well, thank you for the advice, Trevor.
但我不觉得我会那么做
But I don't think I'm going to do that.
迈克  人生走得越远
Michael, the longer you go,
钱就越不重要
the less the money matters.
食物不再美味
The food doesn't taste as good.
车不再够快
The car isn't fast enough.
视野不再够高
The view isn't high enough.
最终你会发现
And finally you realize
你愿意付出一切
that you would trade it all in
换取一夜  能好好躺下来
for one night of going to bed
完全不用担心
where you don't have to worry,
"他们什么时候会来抓我"
"When are they gonna come for me?"
你差点被抓  是吗
You almost got caught, didn't you?
没有  我只是受不了了
No, I didn't. I just couldn't take it any more.
最终我去找了个人聊了聊
So finally I went to talk to someone.
是谁
Who?
你知道是谁
You know who.
我得走了
I gotta go.
保重  迈克
Take care, Micheal.